# JESSICA J. MONTERO

## TECHNICAL & ONPAGE SEO + WEB DEVELOPER

I have over 4 years of experience developing and managing websites projects, from their conception through to implementation, maintaining approach on SEO and analytics web for after the merge provides all the tools to the Marketing and Sales team.



#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Webmaster + On-page & Technical

#### Working in the Redwoods

May 2020 - Apr 2021

**Ecommerce Website** 

# Webmaster + On-page SEO Secartys | CICAT | SmartTech | Solartys

Apr 2019 - May 2020 Corporate Websites

# Web Designer + On-page SEO Lola de Miguel

Mar 2018 - Sep 2018 Personal Brand Website

# Web Designer + On-page SEO

## Terractiva

Dic 2017 - Feb 2018 Corporate Web

#### **EDUCATION**

#### UX / UI

Apr - May 2022 Udemy

# **Bootcamp Full Stack Developer**

Jul - Oct 2021 Aulab Academy

### **Google Analytics**

Nov - 2020 | ID 61974930

# **Technical Degree in International Trade** 2012-2014

Centre Lopez Vicuña · BCN

#### TECHNICAL SKILLS

#### SEO & WEB ANALYTICS

Semrush · Screaming Frog · Yoast SEO · Google Search Console









Google Analtytics · Google Tag Manager · Google Data Studio







#### WEB DESIGN

Figma · Visual Composer · WordPress · WooCommerce · Mailchimp











#### FRONTEND

 $\mathsf{HTML5} + \mathsf{CSS} + \mathsf{CSS} \cdot \mathsf{Grid} + \mathsf{CSS} \cdot \mathsf{Flexbox} + \mathsf{Sass} + \mathsf{JavaScript} + \mathsf{Git} + \mathsf{GitHub}$ 















#### CONTACT

+34 653 573 982

holajjmontero@gmail.com 08037 Barcelona



in LinkedIn: Jessica J. Montero